(New Me)
(New Me?)
- Nice to see you all. - Nice to see you.
We have an important announcement today.
- What? - My gosh.
- What is it? - What?
- What is that? - All right.
- What? - Pass them down.
- "Newsletter?" - What's this?
- What is this? - It's like passing down test paper.
- It's the newsletter. - My gosh.
I haven't gotten one of these in a long time.
To make it look old-school, I printed it on pulp paper.
- Pulp paper! - This brings back old memories.
So...
- Let's take a look. - Okay.
This looks like a real newsletter.
We'll go on a summer retreat soon.
We'll stay at a youth hostel just like the old days.
- A youth hostel? - We're going to a youth hostel.
It's been so long.
- At last. - I'm excited.
"Verdurous early summer."
We haven't seen a phrase like this in a long time.
It's a community program.
Will you play "By Love" by Sunflower?
(Precious memories with the members)
- I love it. - It's one of the regular meetings?
A retreat?
We'll become one at the retreat. Right?
We'll go on a summer retreat.
What if there's a drill sergeant?
A drill sergeant?
Things we need to bring...
We have to bring a random ingredient for bibimbap.
- This is important. - What's this?
We'll have random bibimbap for lunch.
It's quite trendy among the zoomers.
- What? - We'll each bring an ingredient...
and mix bibimbap.
We can just bring any ingredient?
Just bring one ingredient without discussing.
(I see.)
- Sir. - Yes?
Will Dae Ho...
and Kian84 bring food too?
What do you mean?
(Last fall at the Innocent Moo-Ku Fall Field Day)
(His kimchi fried rice made him speechless.)
It's bibimbap.
(Dae Ho's bibimbap from the dead)
- My gosh. - Goodness.
Unfortunately, that will be the case.
- I have a question too. - Go ahead.
Is it possible to leave out ingredients if we don't want to?
We must add everything.
- Because... - That's...
- We're one. - We are?
Let's not invite Dae Ho.
(Then let's not invite Dae Ho.)
Not Dae Ho.
- Hey. - Even I can't eat his food.
He eats weird food.
It just looked unappetizing. But the food wasn't spoiled.
- Okay. - Wait.
- There will be a talent show. - Yes.
Will there be a prize if you win first place...
or something?
- Actually, - There's a prize?
I prepared the best prizes this time.
You guys might fight over them.
The prizes will be better than the ones at the fall field day.
- Really? - They will be better?
There will be amazing prizes. I daresay they're the best ones yet.
We're meeting up at the MBC building in Sangam at 10am.
We'll leave on time even if you're late.
I have to host a radio show.
Remember the school retreat?
I really love this project.
It's been 30 years since I had been on a retreat.
- Really? - Yes.
- Think about my age. - I haven't used the word,
- "retreat." - Right.
- I'm already excited. I won't... - Me too.
I won't be able to sleep now.
I'll be too excited. I'm serious.
- No more questions, right? - No.
Don't forget that we have some amazing prizes.
- Great. - Thirteen people.
I'm looking forward to it.
(A Lucky Day)
(Snoring)
(It's pitch-dark in the room.)
(Snorting)
That's the kind of sound I make.
(Is that me?)
I snored like that?
Shin Young, you should buy the CPAP machine.
- What's wrong with me? - That's...
- My goodness. - Wait.
- You didn't know you snored? - No.
I thought I didn't snore.
(Getting up)
(She gets up right away.)
(Spraying)
(Getting rid of mites as soon as she gets up)
You do that to get rid of mites.
That's my daily routine.
That's nice.
- I like that you're clean. - We should have a clean lifestyle.
(Frowning)
(She wakes up late past noon.)
Today is my day off.
So I'm having a day off today.
It's been three weeks since I had a day off.
I had a pile of household chores waiting for me.
I only thought about doing them because I was so busy with work.
When I came home, I took a shower and went to sleep.
There's a list of chores I never got a chance to take care of.
I'm going to do all of them today.
(She'll take care of the chores on her day off.)
(Grabbing)
(Let me turn on the AC first.)
Gosh, the temperature at your house is 30°C?
- The temperature is at 29°C? - It's hot in the house.
(Warm)
(Darn it...)
(The house is getting warmer, not cool.)
It must be really hot in the house if it's at 29°C.
(Let me just turn it off.)
(Sighing)
The air conditioner is...
broken.
- It's the cooling gas. - When the weather is so hot?
- The cooling gas? - It ran out of the cooling gas.
I couldn't recharge the refrigerant.
You need to call someone for that.
- Right. They'll come in September. - You need to.
What? Really?
The backlog is crazy.
I bet everyone is calling the engineers now.
I tried to last one summer without the AC.
But I ended up sleeping in a motel.
- I bet it was super cool. - Right.
- I couldn't stay at home. - Right.
So I'm looking into more options.
(Should I open up the window?)
What if it's cooler outside?
My gosh.
(She opens the window and feels the air outside.)
- Gosh, it's hot. - It was super hot that day.
It's really hot in the afternoon.
- I can see it in your face. - My gosh. It was so hot.
- I can feel the heat too. - It drove me crazy.
- Yes. - It's hot.
It's hot.
(She runs away to the bathroom for now.)
(Washing her face)
(Scrubbing)
It cools you down only for a minute.
(She quickly washes down the heat.)
She should splash some water on her back.
What?
- Are you washing your hair? - Yes.
I bought that faucet,
so I could wash my hair over the basin.
- So you can freely move it around? - Yes. That's right.
Look at the back of her head. It's smooth.
- I shaved it. - I see.
(She shaves the back of her head herself.)
You wear a Two Block haircut.
(It's still smooth as she shaves it herself.)
(Scrubbing hard)
(Thoroughly cleaning it with shampoo)
(Rinsing her smooth nape completely)
That's not Sung Hwan.
Just in case you didn't know.
When I was watching it, I was like...
- That's not Sung Hwan. - "Wait. When did I film that?"
That's not Sung Hwan.
It's Shin Young.
(It's Shin Young with a shaved nape.)
What's this?
All right.
(Oh, that's nice and cool.)
(She brushes her teeth too.)
(Retching)
- That's not me. - It's not Sung Hwan.
- It's not me. - That's not Sung Hwan.
(It's me.)
My gosh. Let's see.
(After cooling down in the bathroom, she goes to the kitchen.)
(I need to eat even on a hot day.)
(Opening up)
(She grabs an ingredient without hesitation.)
What's she going to eat for her first meal?
- Pork belly. - Pork belly.
I just woke up, so...
(I love it.)
I always eat pork belly in the morning.
It's either pork belly or bulgogi.
Or I eat braised kimchi with ribs.
I often eat meat for my first meal of the day.
(Shin Young's breakfast is full of meat.)
I need energy.
Our breakfast should be as grand as a royal meal.
We must eat like a king for breakfast to be healthy.
Our lunch should be simple like the commoners' meal.
Then our dinner should be scarce...
like the servants' meal from the old days.
But your breakfast and dinner are both grand like royal meals.
You eat like a king for all three meals.
My dinner is scarce like the servants' meal.
You know that servants eat everything they see.
Right.
(Food is the best.)
(An original diet following the hierarchy system)
(Now, it's time for me to sit on the throne.)
(Picking up a thick strip of pork belly)
(Cutting)
This is for breakfast.
(It should be filling like a royal meal.)
(Sprinkling)
(Seasoning it with salt)
(Closing the lid)
(Pressing the button)
(She goes to the fridge after letting the meat get grilled.)
(Grabbing containers)
She's taking out some side dishes for the meat.
Gosh, it smells great.
(Transferring pickled victory onion)
(This time, she opens up the kimchi container.)
My gosh, it's nicely fermented.
Gosh, I love kimchi.
- It's so good. - Yes.
(Transferring it onto the plate)
I have five different types of kimchi.
- This is crazy. - Cucumber kimchi.
- Cucumber kimchi? - Yes.
Next, young radish kimchi.
- Seriously. That's my favorite. - Do you like it?
- That's my favorite kimchi. - MINHO is getting excited.
Young summer radish kimchi.
They're the five different types of kimchi I have.
(Plating five different types of kimchi)
You have so many different types of kimchi like a kimchi expert.
She's like a kimchi researcher.
(Kimchi is ready.)
(Is the meat cooked?)
Good.
Oh, this is crazy.
What is it?
- Is it grilled nicely? Gosh. - It's grilled perfectly.
Isn't this amazing?
It rotates on its own.
I can put the meat in, close the lid,
and do something else.
That's convenient.
I love that the oil doesn't splatter.
How convenient.
I consider the color...
- when I choose a plate. - I like that.
- I like making it look pretty. - Presentation is important.
This is amazing.
It looked like the grilled meat from a barbecue restaurant.
Great.
Nice.
(Nicely grilled pork belly...)
(with pickled victory onion)
- My gosh. - I need my set of kimchi.
- Gosh. - It's making me salivate for real.
(Let's see.)
Thank you for the food. Amen.
(She picks up a piece of the cabbage kimchi first.)
(Taking a bite)
- Gosh, that looks good. - Goodness.
That does look good.
(Yes, this is what I'm talking about.)
She got a headache because it's so good.
Right. I have a headache.
- A headache. - Yes.
(This time, she picks up pickled victory onion.)
(She puts it on top of the pork belly.)
- It must be really good. - The pickled victory onion...
It must be really good.
The pickled victory onion is so good.
(Grabbing it again)
Wrap it up.
(Opening her mouth wider)
My gosh.
(This is pure happiness.)
(Grabbing the black pepper)
- Yes. The black pepper is next. - Black pepper.
I should sprinkle black pepper.
That's the next pairing.
- Gosh, she's one of us. - And...
(Popping it into her mouth)
(A new flavor bursts in her mouth.)
(Getting her 2nd headache)
My gosh.
It was really hot. It was 29°C in the house.
Having pork belly at 29°C isn't easy.
My gosh. Pork belly at 29°C.
But it was good.
(Something is missing.)
(I have no choice.)
What?
You know, I should have bought 2 packs, but I only bought 1.
- She'll make more food... - She'll make something else.
- because the pork fat is in there. - Right.
(I knew you'd get it.)
It's rice.
(Looking over)
- She'll use the pork fat? - Seriously.
- Of course. - Yes.
(She grabs the leftover meat.)
(Cutting it into the pot)
- That's good. - It's so good.
(Next, she adds rice...)
(and kimchi.)
I also added cucumber kimchi.
(This is good.)
(She starts the pot once again.)
All done.
(Her second dish is ready in no time.)
It didn't take long. It really didn't.
- You just need the pot. - Great.
- Okay. - My gosh!
(Transferring the rice into a bowl from the pot)
All done.
My gosh. It's stir-fried nicely.
(She puts it down on the table and comes back to the kitchen.)
(Climbing up)
What's that?
- You need this. - Kelp?
Glass noodles?
(She grabs something else.)
(The food she brought is...)
What's that?
- Roasted gamtae. - Roasted gamtae.
Oh, that?
Yes. It's roasted gamtae.
So gamtae and dried lavers...
are different.
When I'm having kimchi fried rice, I need to wrap it up with gamtae.
This combo...
gives me a rich flavor with a hint of the ocean.
- Is it better than dried lavers? - Much better.
I need to eat rice.
(Scooping up a big spoonful)
- Gosh, that looks good. - Three, two...
(Turning her wrist)
- There you go. - Gosh.
You use different wraps...
- based on the dish. - Of course.
It's a different dish now.
(She can taste the deep ocean in her mouth.)
(The fascinating symphony of flavors)
This was a crazy combo.
- I feel like I'm eating it. - She's an expert.
Watching food clips like this never gave me cravings before.
But your clips are different.
Something is stirring up inside me.
Right.
I want to try the food too.
(Having a sip of the warm broth)
That's doenjang soup with dried radish greens.
- That's just crazy. - Gosh, that must be tasty.
(Satisfied)
My gosh. I can see things now.
(Hitting the spot)
(Fighting the heat with hot soup.)
(Enjoying it)
I figured out why I'm starting to get food cravings...
- from your clips. - Why is that?
You're not rushing.
- Right. - People usually eat fast.
I don't rush my meals.
I have to eat fast when I'm working.
On my days off,
- I want to take my time. - You're eating at your pace.
- Right. - It's...
(Enjoying the warm soup at her own pace)
(Refreshed)
That hits the spot. Gosh, this is a good breakfast.
She licked it clean.
Gosh, it was so good.
I'm so hungry right now.
She looks so proud of it.
It was the perfect meal.
It's the best.
(She starts cleaning up right away.)
- Did you eat the lettuce at all? - What?
I don't think she ate any of it.
Right. There was lettuce.
- It was for the decor. - I see.
- For the decor. - It's like having a plant.
I like that kind of decor too.
I was having healthy food. So I kept the decor healthy too.
- I had some lettuce out there. - Looking at greenery is good...
for your eyes.
- Of course. - It's like having a plant for you.
Exactly. It's like having an orchid.
(It's for decoration only.)
- Wait. - You caught me off guard, MINHO.
- I'm sorry. It looked the same. - My gosh. You...
- You're sharp. - Okay.
(She washes the dishes immediately after her meal.)
Gosh, that was good.
I'm in a good mood.
Having a satisfying meal brings so much joy.
- Food brings so much joy in life. - Exactly.
I must get rid of annoying chores right away.
- Yes. - It's easier that way.
- I do my dishes right away too. - Yes.
- Not putting them off is the best. - Right away.
- Don't put them off. - Don't put them off.
(Wipe every corner of the sink too.)
(Squeezing)
(She finishes washing the dishes in no time.)
All done.
(I should take health supplements after a meal.)
(Manly)
I'm not eating candy.
- You eat it like it's a snack. - Health supplements.
Why is the tumbler so big?
I have a question.
Why do you keep carrying around such a big tumbler?
I drink a lot of water.
This holds up to 1.8L of water.
- Every day... - I thought...
- it was a fire extinguisher. - I drink...
- Why is it so big? - It's way too big.
I host a radio show.
- I don't have time to get water. - I see. For your throat?
That's true.
I'm trying to use my tumbler as much as I can.
I bet you have a tasty drink in there.
You have dried radish greens soup in there, right?
- No. Come on. - Be honest.
Why do you want to check it?
- Wait. - It's water.
- Is it really water? - Yes.
- I don't smell any food. - Exactly. There's no smell.
- It looks tasty. - It's water.
What is it?
(2 hours have passed already.)
You ate your meal for two hours?
Time flies when you eat.
Time flies by.
(Shin Young comes out with a hat on.)
Is she going somewhere? No?
- Is she going out? What? - She's going out?
(The homebody, Shin Young, finally leaves the house.)
- She's not going out. - She's not going out now.
- I came back in. - She came back inside.
(She comes back home right away.)
(Staying at home on a day off is the best.)
Yes.
(Instead of going out, she grabs a box.)
(She sits down on the floor with the mystery box.)
(Popping it open)
What's that?
What is it?
I'm nervous.
- What's that? - What is it?
(Mysterious long objects)
(Let me see.)
(She starts assembling them.)
- Wait, it's curved. - That's...
(Wait, it's curved.)
I've been meaning to do this for a long time.
- I finally got around to it. Yes. - You're doing it on your day off?
- I guess she wanted to do this. - I wonder what it is.
For some reason, I can't wait to find out.
(A curved object is starting to take shape.)
I thought about...
buying this since April.
My feed was basically plastered with this.
I thought this was a revolutionary product.
I even submitted my personal customs clearance code.
I was like, "I did it."
I had to wait for a month to get my hands on this product.
- It came from overseas? - Yes.
It's the window cleaner.
Windows? To clean the windows?
For the exterior of the windows.
- I see. For the exterior? - Actually,
we can wipe the inner windows whenever we want.
There are pine resin and dust outside.
It's so dirty.
- Right. I wanted to clean that too. - Yes.
I saw so many clips like this one.
I can wipe the exterior of the windows from my home...
with the minimal movements.
I bought the mop.
All right.
(Let me get started.)
(Grabbing)
- You add water to it. - I see. You need to add water?
(Mixing the soap water)
(Filled with excitement, )
(she sets up the new mop.)
I've been waiting for it since April.
That was a long wait.
This product was sold out after its initial release.
- Really? - I bought after the second release.
It's an innovative item.
(Hyped up to the max)
(She carefully pushes out the new mop.)
After that...
(She slowly pushes it.)
- What's going on? - What?
- It looks like a bean sprout head. - This is stuck.
Gosh, did I buy the wrong one online?
(Struggling)
My gosh.
(She fixes the angle and tries to push it.)
Wait.
(The more she pushes, the wider the dirt stains smudge.)
- It's getting dirtier. - It's getting dirtier.
You can't see out the window now.
- It's gotten murkier. - A privacy protection window.
(The more she wipes, the tighter security grows.)
I might be doing a bad job.
I should turn it.
(There's no way my revolutionary item will disappoint me.)
This must be it.
(Sounding certain)
(Pushing)
This is it?
You have such short arms.
My window didn't open all the way.
- I get it. I see your problem. - Right.
That's not going to work.
- If it stains... - It might be useful for Sung Hwan.
- I... That's good. - The window slides all the way.
It'd be easier if it were a full-length window.
I just think you don't know how to work it yet.
I should look up how to use it.
(Taking a step back)
I have this habit of not reading the manual.
- Same here. I don't read them. - Right.
This time around, I read it after scanning the QR code.
(Tapping)
(To make matters worse, the video is in Chinese.)
It felt like I was watching "A Better Tomorrow" all of a sudden.
(A Chinese listening exam begins without any warning.)
You just need to check the posture...
- without the explanation. - You don't need...
(As she needs help, she starts watching.)
I attached it too.
(Super focused)
(The explanation continues in Chinese she doesn't understand.)
(Stopping)
- What? - That's it?
- You could assemble it. - He didn't show me how to use it.
He only showed you how to assemble it.
- Right. - Not how to use it on windows?
- He didn't show me that. - He didn't do that in the video.
Right. All I understood from the video was "hello."
(Dumbfounded)
I waited a month for this. This is bad.
It's not easy.
Let me try it.
(Let me try it.)
"Clean your windows easily."
(I must finish cleaning the windows on my precious day off.)
(Pushing down)
This...
What is this? Darn it.
It's gotten dirtier, Shin Young.
(Dirty)
What is this? It's nothing like what I saw in the video.
Gosh, I'm never buying this again.
See? It was different from the video.
Why isn't it working?
My gosh. What is this?
(Shaking)
Gosh, I think it could work.
I think so too.
You might have to move it...
- like you're sawing. - Right.
Or you should hold just the bottom part in your house.
- Gosh, I'm never buying this again. - You do have a short reach.
- Yes. I'm too short. - You know?
I waited a month for this.
(Feeling dejected)
I'm never buying this again.
According to the videos I saw,
it should stick to the window and I should be able to wipe it.
When I put it over the window...
I don't know what happened. Maybe, the mop was upset.
- The head of the mop was sulking. - It went like this.
- I was so upset. - Seriously.
Later, I tried to wipe the bottom window.
I thought my rotator cuff was going to tear off.
Criminals get arrested by the FBI with their hands behind their backs.
It made me wonder if that was how the criminals felt.
Everyone says not giving in is the way to go.
But I gave in completely.
(Zero motivation)
- It was a mess. - Nothing went well that day.
- There are days like that. - Of course.
You must be upset.
- You waited for a long time. - Right.
- Wasting time is the annoying part. - I was upset for sure.
But I discover useful items...
after several failures.
Of course.
(Wringing)
What's this?
I can just wipe it like this.
I used my bare hands instead.
- Not the mop. - You can only wipe that part.
(She ends up abandoning the mop and using her bare hands.)
My gosh. I didn't know the stains smeared on my arm.
(Her arm is messy with stains.)
(I should at least wipe the windowsills thoroughly.)
My gosh. Yes. It looks clean enough.
All done.
(The windowsill looked blackish.)
- It's clean. - It's clean now.
- Gosh, I love it. - It's not easy...
to clean the windowsill spotless like that.
(Impressed)
(The window was stained with dust.)
(It's gotten a unique look.)
I have to hope it rains soon.
- The rainy season will last long. - You ruined it.
Neat freaks like Shin Young would hate seeing that.
- Gosh, I don't want... - Seeing stains on the window...
- to look out the windows now. - Exactly.
I couldn't understand the reviews since they were in Chinese.
(Lamenting)
Gosh, I learned a lesson.
I learned a lesson.
This was a good lesson I learned.
- Did you throw it out? - No, I just put it away.
I actually want it.
I'll give it to Sung Hwan.
- No way. - I actually bought two.
- Thank you. - I bought two.
(It might be useful for your house.)
It's been an hour.
(I tried to wipe the windows for an hour. How upsetting.)
(Opening up)
- She used it as an excuse to eat. - What's that?
I was sweating and it wasn't working, so...
- Did you want a cold drink? - Yes.
- There was no air conditioner. - That's right.
- That's right. - I forgot about that.
- After the failed attempt... - When there is no air conditioner,
- even standing still is exhausting. - That's right.
(To a cup that's full of ice cubes)
- Zero sugar. - Yes.
It must be cold.
(It goes straight to her throat.)
(Exclaiming)
- It's cold. - That's the taste.
That's right.
On some days, Coke tastes better than a meal.
(It washes down the frustration from cleaning the windows.)
(A glass of cold soft drink)
What now?
(She takes something out once her stomach is settled.)
(I need to move busily to finish the chores on my day off.)
(Heave-ho)
(She moves the piled-up shoeboxes to the living room.)
Those must be shoes.
Throwing away the shoebox seems like a waste.
- It's a waste. - That's right. I don't know why.
- Right? - That's right.
(The boxes pile up in no time.)
The shoeboxes were piling up...
because I didn't know where to put them.
These days, I really want to try...
creative craft.
Instead of buying a new item, I wanted to use what I had...
to create something new.
Using the items at home,
(What can I make at home?)
I wanted to make something.
I wanted to recycle. So I decided to use...
the shoeboxes I had collected...
to make a dresser.
It's fun to watch you craft.
- See that table with stickers? - I think it looks really cool.
I made it myself.
- That's a bit... - Yes.
It's a vintage table.
Using shoeboxes, I'll make a dresser.
You want them to slide out like drawers.
That's right.
Using shoeboxes?
(Curious)
(She cuts the top to make the compartment.)
(Let's see.)
It doesn't fit.
(It doesn't fit.)
(Flustered)
- Are the shoeboxes the same size? - That's right.
- Don't they need to be different? - That's right.
(Smart CODE KUNST)
(She tries it with a different box.)
(Thankfully, the size is perfect this time.)
(The compartment can be pushed in and out.)
(Can I glue them together like this?)
(Let's see.)
(But the boxes have slightly different heights.)
This isn't what I planned.
(Flustered)
Then...
(The dresser faces a crisis.)
(I can't...)
- "I can't." - That's genius.
(What should I do?)
The boxes were supposed...
to go into other boxes prettily.
But they didn't go in since they were the same size.
So I decided to make a table...
where I could display a plastic model...
and got to work.
A table for a plastic model?
When something doesn't work, I give up quickly.
- That's a good habit. - I give up quickly.
If I try to make it work,
- my entire day will be wasted. - And you'll get stressed out.
That's right.
I'll go with the initial plan.
(Loading up the glue gun)
- You have that at home? - Yes.
- She put the boxes together. - Yes.
(She begins building without hesitation.)
That goes on the bottom.
(After giving up quickly, she works just as quickly.)
You're like MacGyver.
(She stacks up the boxes to make a display table.)
(She puts on her glasses to focus on the craft.)
(She creates the idea that enters her head.)
(Sighing)
(I think it's pretty much done.)
(Let's put it on display.)
That's right.
- It works. - What? It looks pretty.
(The light comes on.)
It's like a display table.
- That's right. - I see.
It looks legit.
Let's turn off the lights.
- You should turn off the lights. - That's right.
(Shining bright)
(It makes them exclaim.)
- Doesn't it look nice? - It's pretty.
- The LED light is pretty. - That's right.
- It's a good idea. - You made an atmospheric piece...
- using shoeboxes. - Doesn't it look nice?
Such pieces of furniture can be expensive.
It looks really cool.
Not bad. It's pretty.
(She failed to make a dresser but managed to make something else.)
Shin Young, it's pretty.
- I know. - It's hip.
Gosh, it sets the mood.
(I can't believe I made it myself.)
- It's so pretty. - It's nice.
- It's cool. - I love it so much.
I'm 100 percent satisfied with it.
I thought of what to do next.
You know the building blocks, right?
I want to put them on top.
(Satisfied, she came up with a plan for the next item.)
(After appreciating the table, she turns the lights back on.)
Let's vacuum the floor.
(Cleaning up after herself)
(Clean)
Good.
It's the evening already.
- Time passes very quickly. - The entire day passes in a blur.
It's time to eat dinner, right?
(It's time to eat dinner, right?)
- Don't guess! - Did he guess correctly?
No!
- "Don't guess?" - Don't guess!
He didn't guess correctly.
- I want to see you go outside. - Hold on.
I go outside.
- I do that. - I was joking.
I go outside to go to work. Don't guess.
- "Don't guess?" - Don't guess!
All right.
- Go outside the front door. - She doesn't go outside.
- She opened the fridge door. - I opened the fridge.
To Shin Young, that must be like the front door.
That's right.
(Moved)
All right.
What's that?
- Jjolmyeon. - Jjolmyeon.
It's jjolmyeon, right?
She hasn't had noodles today.
All right.
(She boils water in a pot.)
(Picking up)
(Bulk jjolmyeon noodles)
- Why is there so much? - Isn't that too much?
It's like the morning routine at a snack bar.
Seriously.
(She untangles the jjolmyeon noodles first.)
(She rinses them expertly.)
(Washing)
Let's go.
(She puts them in the hot water.)
(Boiling)
(Heave-ho)
(Boiled jjolmyeon)
(She quickly rinses the noodles in ice water.)
That process makes the noodles chewy.
(Chewy jjolmyeon is ready.)
It's my recipe.
- I'm curious about your recipe. - The broth must be icy.
It's the naengmyeon broth...
- you can buy at a store. - Okay. Naengmyeon broth.
- Buy that. - That's right.
(She opens the fridge again.)
Young radish kimchi.
- Can you tell from the container? - He can tell.
It isn't like that. Young radish kimchi...
- gets added to jjolmyeon. - That's right.
Yeoljjolnaeng.
Young radish kimchi,
jjolmyeon noodles, and naengmyeon broth.
That's why the name is...
- yeoljjolnaeng. - Yeoljjolnaeng.
- Yeoljjolnaeng? - Yes.
The thing is, I have a philosophy.
I don't add glass noodles to a cold dish.
(She has added glass noodles to all sorts of dishes.)
(Her favorite)
The temperature was 29°C,
so I couldn't eat a hot dish.
I had to eat a cold dish.
Eating a hot dish...
- would've killed me. - That's right.
(She was destined to eat a cold dish today.)
I substitute glass noodles with jjolmyeon for a cold dish.
I eat glass noodles in the other three seasons,
but I eat jjolmyeon in summer.
(On top of jjolmyeon that got an icy shower)
The kimchi container is huge.
It looks tasty.
(A heap)
- That's it. - The kimchi broth.
The kimchi broth is a must.
(My mouth is watering.)
- It's a must. - I'm so hungry.
- This is driving me crazy. - Look at that dish.
It's so simple.
You use the store-bought broth and dried laver.
(Adding dried laver)
- Dried laver. - Seasoned dried laver?
Yes. Dried laver.
- You can't use gamtae for this. - Dried laver.
- Sesame. - You sprinkle a lot of sesame.
- Sesame makes everything tasty. - Sesame oil.
- Sesame oil. - You add a bit of sesame oil.
That's right. Plum syrup is a kick.
I didn't know that.
- It's sweet and sour. - I always add it.
It's really tasty.
(It looks delicious.)
(Rushing to the table)
I love it.
- Pepper is a must. - Pepper. Okay.
- I always add pepper at the end. - To that dish?
- Of course. - It's a must.
- It looks amazing. - Do you know why?
- Jjolmyeon has the taste of flour. - That's right.
- I know. - Pepper eliminates that taste.
- Really? - Yes.
(She turns on the TV as if it's a ritual for a meal.)
All right.
(Mixing)
- It's a soccer channel. - A soccer channel.
I watch all the matches.
Do you know what surprised me?
Her algorithm is identical to mine.
Except for food, right?
Except for food.
Regarding food,
- it's identical to mine. - The three of us...
have common grounds.
Mixing Sung Hwan and CODE KUNST will give us Shin Young.
All right.
(She prepares to eat yeoljjolnaeng as she watches soccer.)
(Oh, my...)
This is insane.
It looks so tasty.
Firstly...
(Slurping)
(Exclaiming)
(Impressed)
(Jjolmyeon finally goes into her mouth.)
(Slurping)
How do we have the same taste in food?
It tastes amazing.
(Becoming emotional)
(I'm close to tears.)
(I worked hard all day long today.)
Since the house is hot, the dish must be twice as tasty.
- It must be like that. - You're right.
Eating the dish relieved all the stress.
(She inhales the dish to relieve her stress.)
Gosh, it's cold.
It cooled my throat...
- Gosh, it's cold. - better than Coke.
She really knows what she is doing.
Many people add naengmyeon noodles to the naengmyeon broth.
- But she adds jjolmyeon. - I add jjolmyeon.
She knows what she is doing.
- Is it that impressive? - The thick noodles have texture.
- It's a revolution. - It's a revolution.
- A revolution? - Yes.
(The revolutionist inhales without hesitation.)
- Wait a second. - The food particle is all natural.
I'm inhaling food.
(She enjoys the summer treat, yeoljjolnaeng.)
- My goodness. - My mouth is watering.
It looks so delicious.
I really want to try that dish. Yeol...
- It's yeoljjolnaeng. - Yeoljjolnaeng.
- Young radish kimchi. - That isn't a washbasin, right?
(She drinks from the bowl.)
You can eat naengmyeon in a washbasin.
(My goodness)
I feel the happiest right now.
It was so tasty.
Even though I made it, I was impressed.
We need to treat ourselves.
I've been staying up all night these days...
because of work.
That's why I'm still bloated.
So I decided to treat myself.
(She treats herself to reduce puffiness.)
- You'll drink all the broth. - Of course.
You must've sprinkled so much sesame.
It stays on your mouth even though you keep wiping it.
It's because my hands have gotten fat.
I lost the delicate touch.
(She washes the dish right away.)
- There is only one dish to wash. - That's right.
- That's right. That's the best. - As for the pot... That's right.
It's so convenient.
(She prepares another bowl.)
- Another bowl? - It's a different bowl.
- It's a different bowl. - Stop it.
- The size... - It's like the shell game.
- Why do you keep... - It's a different bowl.
Will you make something else?
(She pours in flour first.)
(Then she adds glutinous rice flour.)
(She takes out the kimchi container from the fridge.)
Think of it as a Korean pancake.
- Will you make kimchi jeon now? - Yes.
It doesn't take much time.
(Will she eat kimchi jeon after having a meal?)
(Shin Young sets out to make kimchi jeon after yeoljjolnaeng.)
Think of it as a Korean pancake.
(She slices kimchi first.)
You need to mix aged kimchi and regular kimchi...
- in equal measures. - Do you need to mix them?
If you only use aged kimchi, there won't be any crunchiness.
- The texture. - To give the flavors depth...
(She mixes two types of kimchi to give the flavors depth.)
(She also adds the kimchi broth!)
Kimchi broth.
I call it kimchi hotteok.
Whenever my grandma made jeon,
she added glutinous rice flour.
I like it when jeon is thick and chewy.
My taste became the same as my grandma's.
(Rushing over)
- A different person came out. - Yes.
(She goes back to the kitchen after changing.)
(Pouring)
(She adds a bit of water to the kimchi batter.)
(Then she mixes the ingredients.)
(Let's see if it's seasoned.)
(Satisfied)
(Satisfied with the taste, she gets ready to fry the batter.)
(Humming)
My goodness.
- You need to make it small. - It isn't big.
Shin Young must be a true baseball fan.
It's 29°C inside the house, but she puts on the uniform...
- to watch baseball. - Of course.
The midsummer heat can't stop me.
But she doesn't watch baseball.
I watch it!
- I watched it! - She never looks at the screen.
(She only focuses on the kimchi hotteok.)
Nice!
See? I watch baseball.
- She watched it for 3 seconds. - She watched it for 3 seconds.
(As she watches baseball, )
(the hotteok factory picks up the speed.)
It looks so tasty.
Shin Young, are you cooking for the holiday?
(She has 91 days to go until Chuseok.)
It's the holiday, but people aren't gathering around.
(She gets ready for the holiday a bit early.)
(I'll have a satisfying meal.)
(She crosses the living room...)
(and goes to the sewing machine.)
It's my workroom.
(For the last chore of the day, )
(She goes to the workroom where she altered her shoes.)
Now...
(She picks up the clothes in the living room.)
I guess she'll attach kimchi jeon to those clothes.
- Why would I do that? Come on. - She is a true artist.
The collar is stretched out.
(Let's turn them into something new.)
I have clothes I wore too often...
and stretched out the collar.
Using polyurethane thread, I'll give them new life.
- Will you fix them? - Really?
I bought this T-shirt, but the collar got stretched out.
- It happens. - So I stitched...
- the back like this. - Most people do that.
- But it became wrinkly. - It happens.
So I put the collar like this...
- and stitched it. - It doesn't work, though.
I thought it might look good,
- but it just came out shabby. - Exactly.
You just need polyurethane thread.
I'll watch and learn.
(I'll see how she does it.)
All right.
(She solemnly sits in her workroom.)
(Let's see.)
Shall I begin after eating one piece?
- One piece. - It's turning into a kitchen.
It's my workroom.
I eat a lot in my workroom.
(She makes preparations by opening a bag of dried laver.)
(Licking)
(Putting)
That's it.
You wrap it in dried laver.
If you wrap it in dried laver,
- it becomes very delicious. - It looks so tasty.
That's why you said you eat it like hotteok.
(She puts it in a paper cup and takes a bite.)
In a paper cup? You know what you're doing.
- Exactly. - She is unbelievable.
(In awe)
(This won't do.)
(I don't need this paper cup.)
(She eats it with her hand.)
I can't believe it.
How did you come up with the idea to eat it with dried laver?
Adding the dried laver is a revolution.
If you eat it with dried laver...
- You normally dip it in soy sauce. - That's right.
(It's tastier since she is watching baseball.)
(Thus, she eats one piece after another.)
(She continues to annihilate the kimchi hotteok.)
- Won't you work? - When will you upcycle the clothes?
- When will you work? - Let me eat first.
(I'll eat just a bit more!)
The problem is, you can't stop once you begin eating.
- That's right. - Yes.
(Gnawing)
Shall I get to work?
(Finally!)
(Grabbing)
Polyurethane thread is enough...
to fix the stretched collars in autumn and winter clothes.
If you study the lining of the collar,
it has two layers.
Make a small hole in the collar...
and put the thread through it.
If you put the thread through it and pull it up,
the collar will become wrinkly.
Once the collar is smaller, tie a knot...
and stitch up the hole.
Once you stitch up the hole, it's over.
- It isn't that hard. - It isn't hard at all.
You don't need to buy new T-shirts.
- It's a good tip. - It's a very good tip.
I can wear it now.
(The stretched collar)
Look. That's how it was before.
It's tight now.
The collar is tight now.
Once you wear it... The collar is wrinkly now, right?
- It'll become smooth. - It'll become smooth.
- It'll become smooth. - Yes.
(I'll work on the rest of the clothes.)
(She picks up the next target right away.)
(She's fully focused on the upcycling...)
(with the strength from the kimchi hotteok.)
There's always a bad day for someone.
Try at least one kind of food...
that you like.
The necessities of life. Clothing, food, and shelter.
Food is right in the center.
Even when you feel really annoyed,
(The upsetting heat in the morning)
you can feel happy after eating pork belly.
The shoe box work that I wanted to do...
was so annoying, but I ate the yeoljjolnaeng,
and it tasted so good.
The yeoljjolnaeng was the highlight.
I was able to get the taste I wanted.
That makes everything fine.
Today was a lucky day.
(Today was a lucky day.)
- Shin Young is really positive. - Right.
(For a good finish to a perfect day)
(Eating again)
(A Lucky Day Made by Myself)
(I Live Alone)
(Teacher's Grace)
- Teacher? - Teacher's Grace.
White clothes.
(Ji Hyeon is sorting out his summer clothes.)
- It's my dressing room. - It's neat.
Right. You have quite a lot of clothes.
- I have a lot more than you think. - Right.
I'll keep the black clothes together as well.
Wait. Are you sorting them out by color?
Yes. I gave it a try.
(He's sorting out his wardrobe by color.)
(Grabbing)
What's that?
- A fabric spray for the clothes? - Right.
(What should I wear today?)
(Rushing out)
(He heads out to welcome his guest in a hurry.)
- CODE KUNST! - I found this outside.
Oh, right.
(The guest is CODE KUNST.)
- What? - I found this.
Right. Yesterday...
Ji Hyeon! You're meeting everyone except for me!
That's not true.
You're meeting everyone else except for me.
- He started with you. - Right.
(The two started as the Hero Brothers.)
(Ji Hyeon didn't know what to do as he had so much respect for him.)
(He became a Fun Run member without Kian84 there.)
- What's going on? - Gosh.
I treated you so well!
You should come to my house as well.
- What? - You should invite me first!
- I will invite you. - Right.
- It's our first encounter. - It's our first encounter.
It's CODE KUNST.
Sung Woo looks so impressive with the way he dresses.
He's the perfect model of a person from Seoul.
I wanted to follow...
a bit of his style.
That was why I asked for his help.
(The impressive guy who makes everything look good.)
(He looks really nice.)
(Amazed)
He fell for him.
(I told my stylist that I wanted to dress like you.)
(Let's go shopping together!)
(Yes!)
So that was when I made a mistake!
(Joking)
I have a clear memory of that mistake.
- Did you always have that thought? - Yes.
I always thought that you looked great in your outfits.
Your style is what to go after.
(Including the classic dandy look, )
(he can pull off the freewheeling street fashion look.)
(Ji Hyeon fell for CODE KUNST's fashion style.)
Who took all of those photos?
Sung Woo is the only one I see on Instagram.
(It's not only himself that he styles.)
(Even the fashion terrorist...)
(transformed into a fashionista through his hands.)
(Thanks to CODE KUNST's styling, )
(he regained his confidence.)
(The representative figure of the boyfriend look)
The one with a good feel.
I'm curious to see CODE KUNST's style on Ji Hyeon.
Come in.
It's been a while for me to visit someone else's house.
- Really? This is my house. - Yes.
Why is it so humid?
Well...
- It's for his throat. - It's for his throat.
The air conditioner is on as well.
It's the house of a macho.
I have this at home as well.
- Right? - Yes.
(Peeking)
What's wrong with your socks?
They're for the shoes I wore today.
Your shoes are split up.
He wore unique socks.
They looked like hooves.
I knew about them,
but it was amazing...
how he actually wore them.
He felt like an FP.
A fashion person.
- Gosh. - FP?
You would've called them toe socks if I wore them.
- Right. - Who wears it is really important.
(Agreeing)
CODE KUNST, I...
I prepared this for you.
But it needs to be heated up.
- What is it? - It's toast.
- It needs to be heated up. - Toast?
I heard you liked bananas and sweet potatoes.
(For his fashion teacher, )
(he remembered his preferences.)
I made a simple toast.
That's cute.
(Toast made with great care)
I'll heat it up slightly.
Your house smells nice.
Right. I used a bit of the spray.
It's a different smell from what I expected.
Everyone who visits my house says that.
There's a certain smell that is felt from a macho.
- It's a bit... - His house smelled really nice.
- My house smells nice. - Really?
I got some cologne for you.
- But... - It's for you.
- Really? I like cologne. - Right.
- I wondered if... - He must get it right away.
What is that?
This is my favorite.
(Impressed)
It was a brand I had never used.
(Amazed by the unexpected gift)
Many people will ask, "Which brand is that?"
Really?
Thank you.
I love cologne.
(He tests it right away.)
(Spraying)
You spray so much of it.
- I do? Is this a lot? - Yes.
- Gosh, that's a lot. - Usually...
Usually, people rub the skin after a few sprays.
(Sniffing)
Doesn't it smell nice?
- It does. - Fragrance is important.
- Right. Especially in the summer. - Right.
I love cologne.
I like trying different scents.
Out of the colognes I'd smelled,
it felt the most luxurious.
It felt like the scent of a trendy person in Seoul.
You and your stereotypes!
- I'm serious. - He's a CODE KUNST lover.
Have it closed.
(This time, it's the gift from the fashion student.)
- You can fold it. - Right.
(Taking a bite)
- It's nice, isn't it? - It's good.
(Feeling proud)
(He takes another bite.)
(Peeking)
I also have milk.
Great.
Was your hair always brown?
- I dyed my hair. - You did?
Why? Was it for something?
No. Since it's summer.
It's been seven years since I dyed my hair.
(Impressed)
Your outfit looks nice today.
(Feeling respect)
- Thank you for saying that. - I'm serious.
There really are hearts shooting out from his eyes.
You want to do everything he does, right?
- Yes. - I know that feeling.
I can totally relate.
I learned fashion from my stylist as well.
- I felt the same way. - Right?
It's been so long to have a younger friend...
act so lovely in front of me.
It felt a bit awkward.
I really wanted to do learn your style.
That was why I kept pausing.
- Ji Hyeon is so friendly as well. - Right.
(Feeling bitter)
- This was what you wanted, right? - Right.
That should've been my place.
(Feeling jealous)
I'm terrible at dressing up.
So what do we do today?
Oh, right. Let's talk about that.
Why did you invite me?
- Well... - You already have...
the looks.
How much more are you trying to style yourself?
Well,
no matter what I wear,
- it feels like I'm trying so hard. - Gosh.
- What does that mean? - It doesn't suit me.
I never felt that.
You were always dressed nicely in the studio.
- That's... - Your stylist?
- Right. That's my stylist. - I see.
I also wear trendy outfits when I go out.
- I'm serious. - Of course.
I wear trendy outfits...
and dress like dancers.
That looks trendy, doesn't it?
These outfits? I see.
Those are just black tracksuits.
(Wearing black puffer jackets in the winter)
I do want to see Ji Hyeon go all out with his outfit.
As I've aged a bit more,
I want to look manly.
- And have your own charm? - Right. And look stylish.
I want to be like that.
This is all I want.
I want to go to Mokpo...
and hear someone go, "What?"
"That person feels like a celebrity."
(That person feels like a celebrity.)
- Without looking at your face. - Right.
- Just by your style. - I really want to hear that.
I get it.
I won't try to make it obvious,
but my style gives it away.
You don't want anyone to notice that you're a celebrity.
Right.
But you want to feel like one with your style.
A neat look with a trendy style.
A manly look as well.
(You know what I'm saying, right?)
That was exactly what I wanted.
- There's good news. - What is it?
This is what I felt.
One's physique is more important than in the past.
You have the physique.
You have the physique...
of a Westerner.
- But... - Yes?
Everyone says that to me.
But when I get dressed,
something feels a bit off.
It's not like I have super broad shoulders.
I don't have super long legs either.
You will understand once you see me.
Have you not seen someone who looks completely off?
(You punk!)
I'm serious.
You shouldn't say that.
All right, then.
Show me your best outfit.
- My best outfit? - I mean,
show me the best choice you can make.
Okay. Got it.
Don't feel too surprised...
- with my level. - Okay.
If it's too high, I'll leave right away.
- I'll go. - Gosh.
- Okay. - He'll dress himself up?
He seemed to be confident.
- He had something in mind. - Right.
Right.
(Rummaging)
Gosh, what do I wear?
Gosh!
(Hopping)
I want to wear something stylish.
(He feels nervous after getting his fashion teacher's mission.)
He looks like an aspiring model.
(He looks like an aspiring model.)
(The teacher is left alone in the living room.)
(Wiping)
- What is he wiping? - What is he wiping?
(He cleans the dust while he waits.)
To be honest, everything needs to be cleaned in your house.
(Being honest)
You couldn't stand it.
Will my back show?
(He moves somewhere else to clean.)
(Dusty)
That's what's cool.
- That's cool? - Didn't he collect them?
But he has to take care of his throat.
That much dust can't be good.
The dust won't fly around because of the moisture.
- You didn't have to clean the dust. - It won't fly around.
- Did I make things worse? - That's right.
(Oh, no!)
(He carries on with his good deed without knowing the owner's heart.)
Okay.
(Mom)
(Why?)
- I keep - He's excited.
This feels great.
(This feels great.)
- Get ready. - Okay.
(I'm coming out.)
All right.
Here.
I dressed myself like that often when I first came to Seoul.
- Really? - Yes.
- You dressed yourself like that? - Yes.
- I'm curious. - It's my favorite outfit.
A lot of my friends wanted the same outfit.
- Really? - I think it will look nice.
I'm curious! How will he look?
Oh, yes!
(Impressed)
(Ji Hyeon shows off his fashion to his teacher.)
This is Seongsu-dong.
(This is Seongsu-dong!)
Oh, yes!
(How do I look?)
(A weak response)
(Unsure)
It looks nice, but... How should I put it?
He can look even better.
Be honest. How do I look? It looks nice, right?
It looks nice, right?
(Slightly expectant)
(Weak response)
There's no problem.
(There's no problem.)
People always give me an awkward response like that.
- The pants fit nicely. - Here's why.
There are too many things on the shirt.
- Is that so? - Right.
There are two pockets.
The buttons are too visible.
It doesn't look bad when seen separately from top to bottom.
But his pants are too fancy.
It doesn't look strange. Never.
Right.
It's a bit too... This isn't it.
Why?
- Why? - Why?
(Rushing back)
He had a few outfits.
How do I look?
- Hold on. - Is this okay?
Let's see this one.
(Looking carefully)
This one...
- Gosh. - Gosh.
(His eyes look busy.)
A farming successor?
(A farming successor this time?)
You can conquer the countryside.
- Right. - The countryside.
(You can conquer the countryside.)
It doesn't suit me, right?
It's not that it doesn't suit you.
I think...
it's important to know...
what fits you nicely.
From my standard,
it will look better if the shirt were bigger.
Or maybe if it were smaller.
It should be completely big or completely small.
Floaty shirts look better...
- when they are bigger. - Right.
(And...)
(And?)
Did you feel disappointed?
He couldn't come up with an answer.
No. I was still thinking.
Shall we begin?
(Getting up)
(He thoroughly checks his clothes.)
Everything he had was standard.
Normal.
I thought that his outfits...
could have more minimalistic designs.
His outfits...
- had lines and such. - Right.
Certain patterns.
If it's for Ji Hyeon with a nice build,
I thought he would look nicer in a simpler outfit.
What? This looks cute.
- This one? - Yes.
There's a hole in the back because I wore it so often.
It's okay. It's fine these days.
New clothes are worn like old clothes on purpose.
- A vintage look? - Right.
- Let's see. - How do I look?
(Let's see.)
Hold on.
- Really? - Yes.
This is something I wear comfortably at home.
I'll be honest, Kian84. You shouldn't say anything.
I'll be honest.
- I can make comments. - Don't say anything.
- Gosh. - You shouldn't say anything.
My gosh!
You don't know my fashion sense.
- It's because he knows it. - My gosh.
- Really? - Yes.
This is something I wear comfortably at home.
It's the nicest thing you have.
(It's the nicest thing you have.)
Really?
- It's the nicest thing you have. - Right.
- Do I leave like this? - No.
I just checked.
Right.
I won't say anything now.
Dress yourself however you want to.
- Okay. - Right.
- But since I'll be with you, - Right.
You shouldn't feel embarrassed to have me around.
No. Why would I feel embarrassed?
I will have you around even if you're in your underwear.
- I'm serious. - Okay.
Okay.
- Got it. - Right.
- Okay. Get changed and come out. - Okay.
CODE KUNST.
- It looks okay, right? - Right.
- It looks okay, right? - Of course.
(His final decision is the white-striped shirt and jeans.)
(Tilting his head)
(Looking carefully)
Okay. Let's go.
I think I know what you want.
Really?
(Along with the fashion teacher that has an idea, )
(he moves out for a field trip.)
You're the only one I'll trust today.
- I'm serious. - Do everything you want to do.
I freed up this day for you.
Okay.
I really...
I really will...
find something nice today.
That will be the only thing I wear.
You're full of excitement right now.
(He's lost for words as he's excited.)
- You look so excited today. - I felt really excited.
(Opening)
- Why? - They're for you.
- Why? - Try them on.
(They're my teacher's sunglasses!)
They're my driving sunglasses.
- It doesn't feel bright right now. - Let me see.
- Do I look okay? - It's to bring up the mood.
Right. You need sunglasses to complete your style.
Right.
Gosh.
- I look okay. - Look at you, Park Ji Hyeon.
I'm an adult now.
(I'm an adult now.)
Don't make Ji Hyeon too much of a Seoulite.
I must become a man of Seoul now.
The song suits you right now.
- Really? - Yes.
- American movie vibes? - Right.
You should...
look outside while resting your chin on your hand.
(Like this?)
There you go. That's perfect.
Why has he become so rebellious these days?
(Rebellious)
He wasn't like this. He looks so rebellious now.
They're striking the same pose right now.
(He's in sync with his fashion guru in no time.)
(Smiling)
Let's go, brother.
You're trying to look too cool now, Ji Hyeon.
It's necessary sometimes.
We're almost there.
- Is that the place? - Yes, that's Itaewon Station.
Time went by quickly as we chatted...
- on the way. - We got there in no time.
(They arrive at their destination in no time with Ji Hyeon learning.)
It's not bad. It's not that hot.
Gosh, it's humid and nice.
(Taking big strides)
The two of you... Gosh.
- We look quite nice. - It's not bad.
Right.
It's nice.
Where are they?
(The center of fashion trends)
(The alley is filled with...)
(showrooms from all kinds of brands.)
(The hot spot that fashionistas from all over the world loves)
(Hannam-dong)
(And the aspiring fashionista has arrived here.)
(Brushing back his hair)
(Impressed)
Gosh, he's so...
He's trying to look cool.
(All about looking cool)
You took a glance at yourself.
Recently, I had a meal...
with Sul Woon Do in Hannam-dong.
But I've never been to that alley.
It was your first time in that neighborhood?
It was my first time in that alley.
I'll introduce them one by one...
on the way.
This is a cafe. It's an expensive one.
Oh, it's a cafe? Not a hotel?
This is a vinyl record store.
This is Alo, an athletic apparel brand.
It's that one, right?
Like Lululemon?
Lululemon is also from the US, right?
- This is a concept store, right? - Yes, for shoes.
It's mostly shoes.
(He looks around for a while as it's his first time there.)
By the way, people here...
all seem quite relaxed.
That's right.
People there seemed free-spirited.
It felt like they didn't care about what other people thought...
and did whatever they wanted.
I liked it.
I liked that.
The mood was like "Roman Holiday."
It felt chill.
The two of you look so cool walking together.
- Really? - It feels like celebs walking.
Thank you.
(Beaming)
Take this, for instance. Even if Steve Jobs...
wears something plain,
people think it's cool.
Just like that, being next to CODE KUNST...
would make people think my clothes are cool.
- He's excited. - They'd think,
"That must be in trend."
- That's... - "That must be in trend."
You had that in mind...
- when we walked together? - Of course.
It felt like people would think I'm stylish too.
That's how I thought they'd think.
(Looking around, thinking he looks stylish)
That's Kian84.
Me? Where?
Kian84 is handsome.
(Impressed)
That's right.
Yes.
He's so hip.
- You looked really handsome. - Yes.
He's always somewhere.
Ji Hyeon, you went to the wrong person.
You should've called me.
- You didn't know the trend changed. - Is that so?
You didn't notice that.
I didn't know there was a photo of me up there.
(Trend84)
He's handsome.
(After seeing Kian84)
- Is this the place? - Yes.
(they enter somewhere.)
Hello!
- Hello. - Hello.
- He wanted to buy clothes. - I see.
- Feel free to look around. - Okay.
(Impressed)
This is what I thought as soon as I entered.
This shop has CODE KUNST's style of clothes.
It felt like CODE KUNST's dressing room.
(The vibe of fashionistas hits you as soon as you walk in.)
What is this place? I've never seen such a place.
(Clothes and accessories in a variety of concepts...)
(fill the space.)
(A concept shop...)
(that the fashion teacher CODE KUNST often goes to)
Let's take a look around the shop.
(Checking out the clothes in earnest following his fashion teacher)
Take a look around and see if you like any.
Okay.
Gosh, this looks good.
(Grabbing a sleeveless shirt)
- There are many bold outfits. - Why?
The shops that fashionistas go to are different.
"Fashionistas?"
I think it'll look good on you.
No.
(Guarding with all his might)
You're still reserved about your style.
(Scratching)
CODE KUNST, I saw your photos...
like these.
I like this kind of style.
- Something natural? - Yes.
A good vibe.
I get what you mean.
Effortlessly cool despite looking grungy.
This one's pretty!
(Following CODE KUNST, expecting to find stylish clothes)
- I think that'd suit you. - That's right.
- The low-cut clothes. - Anything suits him.
- What do you think? - He'd become CORTIS right away.
- What do you think about this? - Isn't it women's?
How is this women's?
I think it's women's.
(His hand flails as if he's lost.)
Honestly, I'm ready to try a sleeveless shirt.
- Even if you don't buy it, - You should just try.
- you'll listen to me, right? - Yes.
This one is really pretty.
(Moving away after answering him)
This is...
This one is pretty too.
He picks clothes with no problem.
You must see it differently than I do.
You should choose too.
Maybe I'll understand your choices after around three years.
No, you...
- Maybe after three years... - No, what's most important...
is that it looks good to you.
(The world of fashion is still hard for him.)
Why do you look so discouraged?
I thought I should accept everything when I went there,
- but after seeing them... - You couldn't try bold ones, right?
Right. After seeing the clothes,
I wondered if I could pull them off.
It's because you're embarrassed.
(He lost confidence after seeing bold clothes.)
I think this will look good on you.
You can wear these shorts with that sleeveless shirt.
It's a sleeveless shirt.
He recommended a sleeveless shirt.
- Does it look good on me? - It's so hip.
- You're just not used to it. - That's right.
My goodness.
What is happening?
The clothes from that shop...
seemed very different from my wardrobe.
- Just try it on. - He's full of concern.
If you were to get clothes similar to your style,
- there's no reason to go there. - That's right.
- He's right. - Yes.
If he went by himself,
- he'd have gotten similar clothes. - That's right.
- The same clothes. - Right.
(Looking around)
You don't wear beanies like this, do you?
- Try on the beanie. - I rarely...
- Let's see. - It's not easy to look good in it.
You look good in a beanie.
- Really? - It suits you well.
Take a look in the mirror.
It's not bad.
- It looks good on him. - Not bad.
(Do I look okay?)
What is it?
- What is it? - I look like a burglar.
- It's because it feels awkward. - No.
You should look like a burglar in a beanie.
I really look like a burglar.
Then you should burgle.
- Does it really look okay? - It looks okay to me.
- All right. - Yes.
All right. Wait.
(Should I try it on like this?)
Yes, you should try it on in different ways.
- Hey, you look really cool. - It's pretty.
- Is that so? - Give up your vision.
(Let's see if this shirt fits your style now.)
It does feel like...
you're in a different field.
- How about... - No, don't do that.
Don't do that.
(Covering his forehead in a hurry)
This is good. Hold this.
- It's a different genre now. - That's right.
- It's pretty. - I was curious, though.
I've never seen Ji Hyeon...
- wear something colorful. - You're right.
Wait.
(Smiling)
Keep getting used to your new look.
(It's not bad, right?)
This is hip, CODE KUNST.
(The more I look at it, the cooler I look, CODE KUNST.)
I feel like I'm following your train of thought.
When you said you look like a burglar, it seemed that way.
- When you said it looked hip, - I know.
It seemed hip.
It's like that for everyone.
It's about your attitude.
He already looks different with and without the beanie.
- You look younger. - I think he looks better it.
- I think you look better in it. - Really?
- You look younger. - I'm keeping up with your thoughts.
Right. I could later think,
- "Why did I find that awkward?" - That's right.
- Hairstyle is part of fashion too. - That's right.
It's hard to find a beanie that looks good on you like that.
Right. It's not easy to find the right beanie.
Is that so?
All five of us should've gone together.
That's right.
Is that so?
Ji Hyeon trusted me with it,
so I picked clothes based on my style only.
This is really pretty too.
Even I'm getting excited.
(Narrowing down his outfit choices)
I felt reassured when you were choosing clothes.
I got it.
Let's try them one by one.
You won't go around in the sleeveless shirt only,
- so don't worry. - Okay.
Try these on.
- "Don't worry." - I...
It wasn't easy to put him at ease.
The clothes...
When I chose clothes for you,
when I tell you to try them on,
you put them on right away.
I put them on right away.
I put them on even if they don't fit me.
You go, "It's mine!"
(Oh, my...)
(Shocked)
This is so cool.
(This is totally to my liking.)
(Blind trust in his fashion teacher)
This...
(If the clothes CODE KUNST picked for him are small, )
(he casually gives up breathing.)
- The teacher. - Whereas Ji Hyeon...
needs an explanation first.
Because you need to reassure him.
I have to tell him why he needs to wear that.
(Ji Hyeon needs absolute reassurance.)
(He sent Ji Hyeon in the fitting room after reassuring him.)
(I hope he likes it.)
But I have sweaty armpits.
I can't help you with that.
You should wear sleeveless shirts since you sweat a lot.
But it runs down.
Run down?
(Coming out)
It looks good.
(Copying the fashion teacher's style)
(Bulging shoulders under the sleeveless shirt)
You look fit.
(And a beanie to add a youthful touch)
(A look carried by a great physique)
- You look cool. - Even your collarbones look good.
He has great shoulders.
You know this shoulder bone?
The sleeveless shirts with straps that sit inward...
- make you look really buff. - That's right.
You look like a boxer.
(Getting great response with the first look already)
You'd look even better in a sleeveless shirt after tanning.
- It'll look good after tanning too. - I think it'll look good too.
I'm really not confident!
It's okay.
(No matter how much I look, I can't get used to this style.)
I look strange!
He finds it really awkward.
This is the best look on you out of everything.
- This? - No, I mean...
We need to develop it further from here.
(Is it okay?)
- It looks good. - He looks much younger.
Yes, you look good.
You feel awkward because you always wear slippers around.
(Is that so?)
I kind of look like the owner of a clothing shop.
The owner of a clothing shop?
- "Welcome. You can look around." - Do you like it?
"Tell me if you need help."
(Laughing)
To Ji Hyeon, a stylish person is the owner of a clothing shop.
- I get the vibe you're after. - Yes, and then...
You should try putting something on top.
He seems really anxious.
(Holding it up)
(Recommending another sleeveless shirt)
It's a sleeveless shirt again.
But... Hold on.
Try this on.
- Try it on like this. - When I get back to my senses,
- it looks weird. - Try it on like this.
Okay. Hold on.
(Trying on the next outfit before self-realization)
Wait. CODE KUNST.
Do I wear this T-shirt on the outside?
Or do I wear the sleeveless shirt outside?
(Laughing)
You should wear the sleeveless shirt inside.
Okay.
CODE KUNST, you went through a lot.
(Checking out next outfit while Ji Hyeon gets changed)
Wait. CODE KUNST.
I think this outfit is quite nice.
(Is that so?)
The color suits him too.
- That looks good on him. - Yes.
- It's cute. - It's cute.
(The slightly visible hem is the key detail.)
I like how the hem is hanging a little.
It's because you're not used to it.
(The mood changed instantly after giving up neutral tones.)
All right, great.
- It's nice. - I told you. It's nice.
He should just buy the exact outfit.
(Approaching)
Should we take a photo of this outfit too?
Of course you should leave a photo of it too.
I'll handle the photos.
(It's a must to leave photos to compare the outfits.)
Hey, this photo turned out great.
Gosh, you look stylish.
He finally found a style of his age.
As for Ji Hyeon,
he sings trot,
so he gives off a mature vibe.
He looks totally different.
I wanted him to give off a young vibe.
It was a little quirky...
but cool.
It was a little bold for me, to be honest.
(Shy)
Actually, I'm still not certain about it.
I still can't decide if it looks good or not.
It's really nice.
I'd vote for Ji Hyeon's old style.
- But... - Why?
Listen, Ji Hyeon.
You don't have to change.
- You can dress in both styles. - You can wear them all.
You don't have to stick to one style only.
I choose the old Ji Hyeon because he tried that on only.
Gosh, that old geezer.
- It's pretty. - It's not bad.
- It looks good. - Yes.
- Right? - You can join the hiphop scene.
(Does it mean it looks good on me?)
I get what you like.
Let's try a neater outfit this time.
Okay.
Since you're tall,
I think shorts like these would look good too.
- Right. - Because he has long legs.
(Not too revealing)
Should I try it on? The owner recommended it for me too.
Yes, try it on.
(A completely different style)
(Amazed)
Shorts look pretty on longer calves.
That's true.
(Looking for clothes that suit Ji Hyeon)
Gosh, this is pretty.
(How do I look?)
- Gosh. - Gosh, this looks good.
- This one looks good. - You should buy it.
How is this?
(Even the teacher is satisfied.)
This is cool.
This is a big challenge for me too.
What do you mean?
Oh, you mean revealing your neck?
(His collarbones are revealed for the 1st time in 30 years.)
I brought a few glasses.
I've never seen you wear glasses, so I brought them.
(Glasses change his look completely.)
You should find your own style.
I think that was a first.
It was a style I'd never tried, so I felt a bit awkward.
My image definitely changes depending on it.
I'm really getting bolder...
in style.
- It's better than I thought. - It's great.
(Boost in confidence)
I like shirts like this too.
What is it?
(He tries on the shirts of his style too.)
He's become more confident.
Yes, it's pretty.
(Ji Hyeon is developing an eye for fashion.)
I look good.
(Feeling proud)
Then... Let's make a decision.
Will this look good on you?
(Finding the best outfit through compromise)
It looked good on Ji Hyeon, though.
I thought this would happen.
He'd buy those clothes but wouldn't wear often.
I thought he'd just keep them in his wardrobe.
It seemed like he prefers...
clothes that aren't too colorful.
I picked clothes with the most striking color...
among the clothes he prefers.
Something more neutral.
I'm so grateful that you were so considerate of me.
You said you wanted to wear it often.
That's why that was important.
Let's try this on for the last time.
Okay.
(The fashion teacher's last choice)
(Peeking)
It looks good.
This is the ultimate boyfriend photo.
Let's try this on for the last time.
Okay.
Not bad.
(Fresh and crisp)
You look good.
(Amazed)
(I look quite nice.)
The look on his face changed.
(Look at his eyes.)
(Between sloppy everyday clothes...)
(and glamorous stage costumes)
(A successful transformation)
This is the best one.
The layered strap that's showing is rebellious.
- Yes, it's me being rebellious. - Something you never tried.
This isn't too pressuring...
- to wear every day, right? - I can wear it.
(He puts on the beanie as well.)
I think it looks good. It's pretty.
(Click)
Is it pretty?
I think this is the best look.
- Right? - Yes.
I like this.
I look like a celeb.
(A style giving off a good vibe)
This looks good. We're all set.
We got it.
(Ji Hyeon's style transformation is a huge success.)
Thank you.
It gave me a sense of freedom.
Should I wear this outfit and go home during the holiday?
If I wear this and go to Mokpo during the holiday,
everyone would stare at me.
"I guess a celeb is visiting." Something like this.
- You are a celeb. - You are a celeb.
You totally are.
(Paying for the outfit he liked as well)
- I'll wear this out. - Oh, okay.
In the end, the clothes I bought from that shop...
- wasn't too challenging, - Really?
- and I can wear them daily. - That's nice.
- You need to compromise. - Yes.
I think I have transformed.
- CODE KUNST. - Yes?
I want to take photos like you do.
- You want pretty photos? - Yes.
- Shall we go to a cafe? - Yes, let's go...
and drink something.
- Gosh, it's so... - They're cute.
Yes.
(He followed CODE KUNST into a cafe.)
Hello.
(Fascinated)
- This... - There was a fascinating cafe.
It's a cafe that gives off a good vibe.
- It's all about good vibes for him. - I'll have something sweet.
I'll have an iced vanilla latte.
An iced vanilla latte.
What would you like to drink?
I'll have an iced vanilla latte too.
Sure.
He doesn't drink coffee like that.
(He doesn't drink coffee like that.)
- About Instagram... - Yes?
I want to do it in earnest.
So you want to take a photo here?
(Nodding)
You have an Instagram account.
I was about to delete everything...
and start anew.
So I wanted to start it in a cool way.
You can fill it with photos like that.
- Yes. - That's right.
You two should meet regularly.
Sit here.
- Is it cool? - Yes.
(The teacher found the perfect photo spot.)
Gosh, this is nice.
(Focused)
Try something more...
(Tilting his head)
I got it. Hold on.
I always did a V-sign when taking photos.
But I met CODE KUNST...
so I could change.
I'm going to keep trying to change.
(A fool who could only do a V-sign)
I think CODE KUNST...
gives off a vibe like this.
He'd go, "Gosh, I'm tired."
Something like this.
To follow CODE KUNST, I should go like this.
(A perfect copy)
Like this.
(He's done analyzing CODE KUNST.)
Does it look like a fashion magazine?
I thought I should relax...
to get photos with a nice vibe.
- There you go. - He's getting the vibe.
Ji Hyeon used to like going fishing with me.
That's good.
What a pretty car.
What do you think?
(CODE KUNST does his best so Ji Hyeon can get a nice photo.)
(Click)
Let's choose now.
(Let's choose a photo.)
(Approaching)
Wait! This looks sick.
"Sick?"
I think it's cooler when my face isn't showing much.
(Sliding)
(Best photos created by CODE KUNST)
- This one looks good. - The one on the right looks good.
It gives off a mysterious vibe.
I think a fashion sense...
is about balance.
You can't wear tracksuits...
and pose like CODE KUNST.
I was really grateful to CODE KUNST today.
Seriously.
He came to my place...
and checked my dressing room too.
Then he went shopping with me and picked clothes for me.
I've opened up to him.
(To CODE KUNST)
(You don't have to knock on my heart.)
He should pave his own way now.
It's so different.
He should go forward by himself.
You're drawing a line again.
There must be a reason people love Ji Hyeon.
I don't think it's always a gain to change oneself.
That was such a good lesson.
Right? The left side of my face...
The more I see him in a beanie,
- the better it suits him. - It suits him.
It looks way better than when he put it on for the first time.
(A Day with a Good Vibe)
(Next story)
(Sung Hwan appears in a huge van.)
(Hey, get in!)
(The 1st Rainbow Club Summer Retreat)
(It's the day of our retreat!)
(Let's go with Driver Ku!)
(Entering the retreat place with excited hearts)
(The theme of this retreat...)
(is cooperation.)
(A day the Rainbow Club members become one)
(They make lunch together with the ingredients they brought.)
(Next!)
(White bags that give off a bad feeling)
(You scared me!)
(That's enough!)
(The rule is to add whatever they brought.)
(Don't forget. We're one!)
- Ready, go. - Go.
(We're stronger when we're together.)
(A place of harmony and mutual care)
(A retreat where they sleep together...)
(and play together)
(The highlight of retreats, talent show)
(The old-school retreat vibe)
(The prize for 1st place...)
(is an opening performance for the Entertainment Awards.)
(Moomoo time to get things in line)
(Screaming)
(They've been waiting for tonight only.)
(I'll show you everything I prepared.)
(Moved)
(Getting sentimental as it's a retreat)
(Teary-eyed)
(A moment when Rainbow Club members become one)
(This is the power of teamwork.)
(We're really happy.)
(The 1st Rainbow Club Retreat)